Camryn Kardos

ckardos@calpoly.edu • (714) 803-2264 • Orange County, CA • linkedin.com/in/camryn-kardos

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

I'm an adaptable and dependable student with an enthusiastic "can do" attitude. I take pride in my passion to explore the topic of leadership to learn more about powerful leaders in our community. My previous internship at Leaderology taught me to push myself in new experiences and how to succeed in projects from start to finish. I am excited to join the workforce and in my next position, I'm looking forward to making a difference in the lives of others.

EDUCATION

California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, CA

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration - Human Resources and Management Dean's List: Winter 2019, Fall 2019, Winter 2020, Spring 2020, Fall 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Client Development Intern, Leaderology, Irvine, CA

June - September 2019, 2020

Graduation: June 2022

GPA: 3.66

- Launched "Coffee with Consultants," a new webinar series to connect company's wide network of consultants
- Strengthened CEO's LinkedIn network using Sales Navigator and increased personal connections by 13%
- Initiated connections with CHRO's to obtain new clients for leadership development programs
- Edited company PowerPoints to create graphics for clients in industries including retail, restaurant, and manufacturing

Wildfire Gymnastics, Youth Gymnastics Coach, Tustin, CA

June – September 2016, 2017, 2018

- Coached young prospective gymnasts how to do basic acrobatic skills to advance their progression
- Executed plans to provide fun and engaging activities for campers to create entertaining weekly experiences
- Facilitated birthday events with 50+ children and consulted with parents in order to customize to themed games and events

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Vice President New Member Operations, Human Resources and Management Association

April 2020 - Present

- Founded club's first Freshman Mentorship Program to help first years acclimate through the college transition
- Recruit freshman students to become a part of a business professional community
- Create content to help guide mentees into becoming better leaders and to prepare collegiate level students for the workforce
- Act as an advocate to support freshman in their first-year experience with advice and helpful materials

Vice President of Recruitment, National Panhellenic Conference

November 2020 - Present

- Direct and plan all aspects of sorority recruitment, managing 3,000 community members, students, and Greek Life officers
- Develop marketing materials to appeal to 1,000 incoming freshman and transfer students
- Manage a \$100,000 personal budget in order to cover the costs of all aspects of sorority recruitment
- Oversee each chapter's recruitment chairs to plan operations of each chapter's recruitment

Panhellenic Delegate Chair, Sigma Kappa Executive Board

December 2019 – December 2020

- Advocate for my sorority's unique organizational needs and represent the sorority's activities and priorities
- Serve as the Panhellenic representative of all chapter relations and committees in weekly meetings
- Represent 224 sisters to the Panhellenic board and foster a positive relationship between our two communities

SKILLS AND AWARDS

Technical and Professional:

Microsoft Office Suite (PowerPoint, Excel), LinkedIn Sales Navigator, Qualtrics: Survey Research

Awards

- Young Woman of Achievement, Beckman High School
- TRU BLU Woman of the Year, Beckman High School
- Associated Student Body Leadership Award, Beckman High School